<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data science on the road</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Data science on the road</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2019, Weru and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:52:59 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinheiro</title>
      <link>/post/pinheiro/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pinheiro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncastillo, Aragón</title>
      <link>/post/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>Population: 650 inhabitants
  Confirmed COVID-19 cases in Spain when we got there: 6,391
  Knowing that the months ahead were packed with work-related travel, Marti was clear about her birthday present this year: a two-day skiing trip close to her home town and a birthday dinner with friends to close it off. We hit the slopes on March 11th, right when the debate about COVID-19 seemed to start heating up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the blog</title>
      <link>/post/uncastillo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/uncastillo/</guid>
      <description>The story of how two development economists based out of Madrid reconsider their priorities after living under strict lockdown for almost 100 days in a rural area in northern Spain. An attempt to make the so-called ‘nomad’ lifestyle work while calculating standard errors, ggplotting, and ultimately promoting evidence-based policymaking.
AndrésCiudad de México, México. 1982
Into Data Science and MEL systems. Cheers for Pumas. Native to La Campestre Churubusco, he would die for some chicharrón prensado while he codes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Andrés Ciudad de México, México. 1982
Into Data Science and MEL systems. Cheers for Pumas. Native to La Campestre Churubusco, he would die for some chicharrón prensado while he codes.
Martina Zaragoza, España. 1988
All about Impact Evaluation and statistical analysis. Trekking, skiing and yoga as second best. Aragón runs through her veins.
Silvio Poccheiná, México. 2015
Walking, eating, sleeping, repeat. Cat and lizard chaser. From the plains of Yucatán para el mundo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>