<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data science on the road</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Data science on the road</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2019, Weru and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:52:59 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bemposta, Algarve</title>
      <link>/post/2020-10-31-bemposta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020-10-31-bemposta/</guid>
      <description>Population: 5 inhabitants
Confirmed COVID-19 cases in Spain when we got there: X
Tracking COVID-19 along the roadBefore deciding where to go next, we mapped the places we had visited so far and realized that geographically, the route had been a little hectic. Aiming to amend this while ‘chasing the sun’ for a few more months, we headed for the Algarve, which would be our first stop on our southern route.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Etorraberri, Euskal Herria</title>
      <link>/post/zestoa/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/zestoa/</guid>
      <description>Population: 4 inhabitants
Confirmed COVID-19 cases in Spain when we got there: 498,989
Something that COVID-19 did not change is the fact that September is a month of change. It means the end of summer holidays and the return to work and/or school. For Marti’s sister, who is a Social Educator (you can check out her profile here), this meant the start of her Master in Intervention with Vulnerable Groups at Risk of Exclusion at the University of Deusto in Donostia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pinheiro, Cinfães</title>
      <link>/post/pinheiro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/pinheiro/</guid>
      <description>Population: 7 inhabitants
Confirmed COVID-19 cases in Spain when we got there: 250,545
A bit of a background here! Back in 2017, we were honoured to become part of the Monitoring, Evaluation, and Learning team for MUVA, an innovative programme aimed to improve access to the labour market for young women in Mozambique. The nature of the work in this project is extremely collaborative and requires constant communication with the local team (+ super fun trips to Maputo!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uncastillo, Aragón</title>
      <link>/post/emoji-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/emoji-support/</guid>
      <description>Population: 650 inhabitants
  Confirmed COVID-19 cases in Spain when we got there: 6,391
  Knowing that the months ahead were packed with work-related travel, Marti was clear about her birthday present this year: a two-day skiing trip close to her home town and a birthday dinner with friends to close it off. We hit the slopes on March 11th, right when the debate about COVID-19 seemed to start heating up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the blog</title>
      <link>/post/uncastillo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/uncastillo/</guid>
      <description>The story of how two development economists based out of Madrid reconsider their priorities after living under strict lockdown for almost 100 days in a rural area in northern Spain. Trying to adapt to this new COVID-19 world, and exclusively visiting low densely populated areas where social distancing can be guaranteed and maximized, this is an attempt to make the so-called ‘nomad’ lifestyle work while calculating standard errors, ggplotting, and ultimately promoting evidence-based policymaking.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>